http://pelicansystems.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Pelican Control Systems
HomeCollaborative RobotsRoboticsSafetyServosDrives Yaskawa Inverter DrivesExtrusionLiquid DosingApplicationContactHomeCollaborative RobotsRoboticsSafetyApplicationLiquid DosingExtrusionDrivesServosHarmonic DistortionContact
Privacy Policy Pelican Control Systems Ltd. respects the privacy of every individual who visits the website and every individual who contacts us. We set out below what information we learn about you when you visit the website, what we do with that information, and how you can change the information we have.What information do we collect and how do we use it?When you visit the website, we recognise only your IP address and not your e-mail address. We will see your e-mail address only if you fill out the online contact form, send us an e-mail message or send us your email address.If you provide personally identifiable information about yourself such as your name, address, telephone number (“Personal Information”) by completing an online contact form, by e-mailing us or otherwise by voluntarily telling us about yourself or your activities, we may collect and retain that Personal Information.If you complete the online contact form or send us an e-mail we will use the Personal Information to provide the information you have requested or other information that we believe will be of interest to you. If you have asked us to contact you with advice or information, we will use your Personal Information to contact you in the manner (if any) specified on the online contact form or communication from you.Occasionally we may use your Personal Information we may notify you about important changes to the website, new services we will be providing, events or articles or other information we think will be of interest to you. We may also use the Personal Information for marketing purposes and market research. This will help us improve our services and the content of the website.If you do not want to receive information from us as described above or wish us to delete or amend Personal Information you have submitted through the website, please use the online contact form to notify us.Non-Personally-Identifiable Information collected automatically.We may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable, such as the type of internet browser and operating system you use, or the domain name of the website or the advertisement from which you linked to the website.When you visit our website, we automatically log your IP address. This is the unique address that identifies your computer on the internet and which is automatically recognised by our web server. We use IP addresses to help us administer the website and to collect data for broad research use. Where possible we link IP addresses to personally identifiable information that helps us evaluate how we might be able to improve our service.When you view the website we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a “Cookie”. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to tailor the website or advertisement to reflect your interests and preferences. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent all Cookies or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored.DisclosureWe may disclose your Personal Information to any of our subsidiary or affiliated companies, to our agents or representatives or to other users of the website for the purposes set out above.We may also disclose your Personal Information to third parties where you request certain services or information through the website. If those services are provided by a third party, that third party may need to have your Personal Information in order to fulfil your request and you consent to the transfer or your Personal Information for the purposes of fulfilling your request.We do and will not sell, trade or rent Personal Information to third parties.We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites even if you access those using links from our website. Therefore we recommend you check the policy of each website you visit.ConsentBy using the website you consent to our collection and use of your Personal Information as stated above. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice to that effect on the website and such change will be effective from the date on which that notice is posted.Our website may contain chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups for to our users or Members only. Any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should always be careful when deciding to disclose your personal information.EffectIn the event of any inconsistency between the Terms and Conditions of this document and the website Terms and Conditions of Use, the Terms and Conditions of Use shall prevail.Pelican Control Systems Ltd.Registered in England No. 3838702 VAT No. 738121445 Terms and Conditions Privacy Policy Tel: (01476) 577708 Some Of Our Partners
